Before you start coding,
在开始编码之前
I wanted to show you what you're going to build in this lesson.
我想展示一下你将在本课程中构建的内容
This is a web app that uses data from the World Bank and outputs a few visualizations.
这是一个使用世界银行数据 输出一些可视化的 Web 应用
Let me show you what it looks like.
这就是它的样子
I've used a few libraries to help me put this together,
我用了几个库 帮我构建了这一切
including Bootstrap to organize the front-end and Plotly for the visualizations.
包括使用 Bootstrap 来组织前端 以及使用 Plotly 进行可视化
In the lesson, you'll build this up one piece at a time,
在本课程中 你将逐步构建该应用
and then afterwards, you can customize this to make it your own.
然后 你可以进行自定义 使其成为自己的应用
Let's start with the first piece of building this HTML.
我们从第一部分 构建这个 HTML 开始
Here on the left is a document with HTML code,
左边是带有 HTML 代码的文档
and on the right this is what the HTML looks like when opening
右边是预览 HTML
the file in a browser like Chrome, Firefox, or Safari.
即在 Chrome Firefox 或 Safari 等浏览器中的打开该文件的样子
I'm actually using a work space in the classroom where I
我实际上是在教室里使用 workspace
can write HTML and then instantly see what it looks like.
其中可以编写 HTML 并立即看到它的样子
You'll be using this same work space to practice writing code.
你将使用相同的 workspace 来练习编写代码
At the end of this video,
在本视频结尾处
I'll show you how to open this file locally on your computer as well.
我将展示如何在本地计算机上打开此文件
HTML is organized into elements that divide up the document into sections.
HTML 是由多种元素组成多个部分的文档
Think of an element as a generic idea,
可以将元素理解为更通用的概念
such as a paragraph,
比如包含所有文字的段落
All of these brackets are called tags.
所有这些带括号的都称为标签
So, if I say the head element,
所以如果我说 head 元素
I'm referring to lines four,
指的就是第 4 行、
five and six of the code containing all of the information about the head.
第 5 行 第 6 行代码 包含有关 head 的所有信息
If I say the head tag,
如果我说 head 标签
I'm referring to the actual HTML syntax with the word surrounded by brackets.
指的就是带括号括起来的单词 实际的 HTML 语法
At the top, the first tag declares the document type.
在顶部 第一个标签声明文档类型
It says that this is an HTML document.
这是一个 HTML 文档
Then comes the HTML element where all the HTML code is written.
然后是 html 元素 其中编写了所有 html 代码
Notice how the HTML element has two parts: a tag that has a left angle bracket then
注意 html 元素有两个部分 一个标签是左尖括号
HTML and then a right angle bracket
html 然后右尖括号
and another tag that looks similar but also has a slash.
另一个标签 看起来相似但其中还包含了斜杠
These are called opening and closing tags respectively.
这两种标签分别叫做开始和结束标签
In this case, the opening tag tells the browser that HTML code is about to start,
在这个示例中 开始标签告诉浏览器 html 代码即将开始
and the closing tag tells the browser that the HTML code ends.
结束标签告诉浏览器 html 代码结束
Everything in-between the start and end HTML tag is HTML code.
开始和结束 html 标签之间的所有内容都是 html 代码
Both head and body have opening tags as well as closing tags.
head 和 body 都有开始标签和结束标签
Everything inside the head tag belongs to the head element,
head 标签内的所有内容都属于 head 元素
and everything inside the body tag belongs to the body element.
body 标签内的所有内容都属于 body 元素
The head element contains a title with opening and closing tags.
head 元素包含带有开始和结束标签的 title
The title of the page usually shows up in a browser tab,
页面标题 title 通常显示在浏览器选项卡中
and the body element contains the book of
body 元素包含了查看网页时
the HTML code that you actually see when looking at a webpage.
可以实际看到的所有 html 代码
You put your website content inside of body elements.
你将网站内容放在 body 元素中
There are all types of elements that can go inside the body of an HTML document,
HTML 文档的 body 可以包含有各种类型的元素
including header elements, link elements,
包括标题元素、链接元素、
paragraph elements, and image elements.
段落元素和图像元素
These elements define your website content.
这些元素定义了网站内容
In this case, I have a header followed by a link,
在这个示例中 我有一个标题 后面是一个链接
then a paragraph, and finally an image.
然后是一个段落 最后一个图像
Notice how all of these elements have opening tags and closing tags,
注意所有这些元素都具有开始标签和结束标签
except for the image element.
除了图像元素以外
Image elements don't require closing tags,
图像元素不需要结束标签
so image elements are an exception to the rule.
所以图像元素是这项规则的一个例外
I formatted the document with tabs so that it's easy to
我对文档进行了一些格式化缩进 这样很容易
see the hierarchical structure of an HTML document,
看到 HTML 文档的层次结构
and I recommend that you do the same.
我建议你也这样做
However, you do not have to format your HTML at all.
不过实际上 HTML 并不是必须要格式化的
The nesting tags structure determines how HTML gets rendered in the browser,
嵌套标签的结构确定 HTML 在浏览器中的呈现方式
not the formatting of the HTML document itself.
而不是 HTML 文档本身的文本格式
I could remove the tabs,
我可以删除缩进
and I'll do that now, and the document would render exactly the same way.
我现在就这样做了 文件将以完全相同的方式呈现
But I'm going to put it back as the way it was.
但我还是会按照之前的方式编写文档
There are many more HTML elements than the ones in this example.
HTML 元素比本例中的 HTML 元素要多得多
These include elements for making lists, forms, and tables.
包括用于制作列表、表单和表格的元素
I'll provide a link below the video where you can learn more.
我将在视频下方提供一个链接 你可以在其中了解更多
It's common to think of HTML as a tree structure.
HTML 经常被视为树结构
The first node is an HTML tag,
第一个节点是 html 标签
and then the head and body tags split off from there.
然后 head 和 body 标签从这个节点分开
The head tag can contain a title tag
head 标签可以包含 title 标签
as well as a few other tags like meta and style tags,
以及其他一些标签 如 meta 和 style 标签
which we haven't discussed yet.
这些我们还没有讨论过
The body will contain headers,
body 将包含标题
paragraphs, images, links, etc.
段落、图像、链接等
Within some of those tags,
在其中一些标签中
you can actually have other tags.
你实际上还可以包含其他标签
For example, in a paragraph tag,
例如在段落标签中
you can have an image as well as a link.
你可以有一个图像和一个链接
Now, take a moment to practice writing your own HTML document.
现在 花点时间练习编写自己的 HTML 文档
You can use a work space in the next part of the classroom.
可以在下一部分使用 workspace
The work space automatically saves your work as you
当你输入代码时 workspace 会自动保存你的工作
type and also refreshes the rendering of your code.
并且还会刷新代码所渲染的内容
I'll add an extra link so you can see what I mean.
我来添加一个额外的链接 方便你理解我的意思
Here, I'm adding a link to the Udacity website,
这里 我添加一个指向优达学城网站的链接
and you can see on the right-hand side that it renders as I type.
然后你可以在右侧看到 随着我的输入显示了对应的内容
As an alternative, you can open any text editor to write
除了这种方案 你还可以打开任何文本编辑器编写
your code and then save the document with the.html extension,
你的代码 然后使用 .html 扩展名保存文档
just like here where it says index.html.
就像这里显示的 index.html 一样
Here's an example. On my desktop, I have a folder,
举例说明一下 在我的桌面有一个文件夹
and inside the folder, I have the index.html and the photo.jpeg files.
在文件夹中有 index.html 和 photo.jpg 文件
If I open index.html with the text editor,
如果我用文本编辑器打开 index.html
you can see the HTML code and I can modify it here.
你可以看到 HTML 代码 我可以在这里修改
If I open index.html in the Chrome web browser,
如果我在 Chrome 浏览器中打开 index.html
I can see the rendered result.
我可以看到渲染的结果
Now, it's your turn to write some HTML code.
现在 轮到你编写 HTML 代码了